http://www.stlukessurreyplace.com/privacy.html

Main Number: 314-542-3300
Admissions Office: 314-542-3338
Email Page
Print Page
Font Size:
Follow us on:
Created: July 18, 2002
St. Luke's Hospital ("COMPANY") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our information gathering and dissemination practices. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact COMPANY at the email address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.
WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
WHO IS COLLECTING THIS INFORMATION
HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED
CHOICES IN THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION
WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED
CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YEARS
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
HOW YOU MAY CHANGE, CORRECT YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION
SECURITY PROCEDURES WE USE
CHANGES IN THESE TERMS
1. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED.
We collect a limited amount of personal information from you in certain areas of the COMPANY website (the "Site") for various reasons. The following is a description of what information is collected:
Registration Information. Registration may be necessary to use certain areas of the Site. When you register at the Site, we ask you for a few items of personal information. All of this information is used to deliver a more personal and pertinent experience for users of the Site.
IP Addresses. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using. COMPANY collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to the Site and to maintain and improve the Site. We do not link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information. We can and will use IP addresses, however, to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Website Terms and Conditions or to protect our service, the Site, customers or others.
Use Of Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that some websites (including the Site) transfer to an individual's hard drive for research purposes. COMPANY uses cookies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on the Site, and make improvements based on the data we collect. COMPANY never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry, especially at websites that provide any kind of personalized service. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Site. The Site's advertisers and other partners may also use cookies in connection with the services and websites to which the Site links. We do not control these cookies.
Top
2. WHO IS COLLECTING THIS INFORMATION.
COMPANY collects the information described above via the Site. In the case of third party features such as advertising, co-branded areas or links to other websites, such third parties may also collect information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. COMPANY is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
Top
3. HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED.
In General. COMPANY uses registration information to learn more about how visitors use the Site and to measure areas of interest. This allows COMPANY to build features and functionality that will enhance your Site experience. We also may use the registration information to filter out those who do not comply with the Website Terms and Conditions. If you so choose when you register, registration information might also be used to send you information about new features and services on the Site or offered by COMPANY or to send you information from selected third party product or service providers. We might also use this information to respond to emails, provide customer support, enforce our Website Terms and Conditions or other similar matters. Aggregate information is also used to help us run and maintain the Site, study traffic patterns and generally learn about the usage of the Site.
Unrelated Companies. COMPANY occasionally shares limited customer information with companies we hire to provide operational, marketing or advertising support, companies that help us distribute our products and services or companies that provide products and services we want to offer. The companies we choose must satisfy our security and privacy requirements. We share your information with these companies only if they agree to treat it confidentially and only if it is legally permissible to do so. We limit the information we provide these companies to what we reasonably believe they "need to know" in connection with their agreement with COMPANY and we don't permit them to use our customer information for any purposes outside our oversight or control.
Government Authorities and Litigation. Sometimes a law, court order or other judicial or administrative process requires us to provide information to a government authority or party to a private lawsuit. We will provide the information that we in good faith believe is required to comply with the law, order or other process. We may also have to disclose certain information in court documents if we have to bring an action against you, for example, to collect a debt you owe us.
Top
4. CHOICES IN THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION.
At the time of registration, you may be given a choice whether you want to receive information about new features, events, offers and special coverage on the Site and about special offers from COMPANY's partners.
It is important to know that you may inadvertently provide personally identifiable information to third parties through your postings to a forum or participation in a chat session, and we have no way to limit their use of the information you may provide. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online (for example, in forums, message boards or chat sessions) that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While we strive to protect our users' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you voluntarily disclose online, and you do so at your own risk.
Top
5. WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED.
Except for your choices described above, we will not knowingly disclose or authorize the disclosure of personally identifiable information (other than aggregate statistical information) to any third party without your consent unless (1) we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Website Terms and Conditions or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) COMPANY's rights or property, other Site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities or (2) we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Top
6. CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YEARS.
In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), COMPANY will not knowingly collect or accept personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13 without prior consent of a parent or guardian. COMPANY will also allow the parent or guardian of a registered user under the age of 13 to review, update, change, delete or refuse to permit further collection of any and all information collected by the Site. A child's personally identifiable information will be treated with the same care and respect as an adult's information. To change, update, review, delete or refuse to permit further collection of your child's information, please send an email to webmaster@stlukes-stl.com.
Top
7. LINKS TO OTHER SITES.
While you are using the Site, you may be linked or directed to other third party websites outside the Site that are beyond COMPANY's control. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of COMPANY. COMPANY is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party websites before providing personally identifiable information.
Top
8. HOW YOU MAY CHANGE, CORRECT YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION.
If you want to change, correct, update or delete your registration information, please contact COMPANY via email at webmaster@stlukes-stl.com.
Top
9. SECURITY PROCEDURES WE USE.
We are very concerned with the security of your personally identifiable information and take great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.
Once we receive your information, we take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your data on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect. We use a combination of technological and policy methods to protect this data. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be aware that COMPANY will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email.
Top
10. CHANGES IN THESE TERMS.
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post notices on the Site at the time of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
If you have questions or concerns regarding COMPANY's Privacy Policy, please email COMPANY at webmaster@stlukes-stl.com.
Surrey Place does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, handicap, or familial status.
St. Luke's Surrey Place - 14701 Olive Blvd. - Chesterfield, MO 63017
Main Number: 314-542-3300
Admissions Office: 314-542-3338
Copyright ©
St. Luke's Surrey Place
Website Terms and Conditions  |  Privacy Policy  |  Patient Notice of Privacy Policies
St. Luke's Hospital
